Wisdom, we pray for your guidance. Father, we thank you that there's a plaque that says,
in you, we trust and Father, we truly do that. Father, a special prayer this evening in the midst of
some impending storms, we pray for safety and so Father again, we thank you and we just give you all praise,
glory and honor. It's in your son's name that I pray. Amen. Amen. Amen.
I am a true judge. I am a pledge of allegiance to the fire of the United States of America
and to the Republic for Wisdom stands. One nation under a God, indivisible with liberty and justice
for all. Thank you. Thank you, Pastor. Okay, I would number four is come again for an unscheduled personal
firm for the United States of Wisdom. I want to say wishes to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
For you, none. I am Fire's Constellant. I am just to have as welcoming item six through eight
for the consent agenda. No, to triple them to Progmayer. And the second. Thank you. All praise. Johnson.
Bless him. All right. Foraster. All right. All right. I am none. Is that paid on ETC? Five or so.
Thank you. How are you? Is your name next? Yes, sir. This is a quick update on the Fibre Survey.
We received the report back on Friday. There was a clear spirit. There were a clear spirit there.
I am here. Okay. We're just trying to start on the issue. I thank you. Put a topic. There was a
916 surveys that were used for the report. So our accuracy is plus or minus 3.2%.
Just I don't want to April 18th. ETC will do their presentation through video conference on the report.
This is going to give you a little summary. A 79% of the residents surveyed. We're wanting a high-speed
fiber internet. So that was very positive. Kind of the thanks for talking to ETC and from the report is
everybody is concerned about the speed of the service, reliability and the price. So that was kind of the concerns.
And I think basically once we get the survey and once both Hicks will look at it,
we'll be able to know if they want to proceed with the concept and then we'll bring those options back to you for action.
Tyler, do you remember kind of what the baseline threshold number was that they felt
in the 40s and 40 to 40 to 40 percent. I take right. I always understood as like 40% of the
potential customers in Miami would sign up with them. And that would give them the ability to
basically cash flow the rest of the project and do the complete build out in Miami.
So based on the preliminary numbers, we're almost done with it. Yes, sir.
Okay. Any questions for Tyler or Dean?
Thank you so much. We'll present that. We'll be ready. Okay. Yeah, next week.
Okay, great. Thank you. Item 19, the acknowledgment of Opital Department of Art and Environmental
Polypermint for construction of 185 in your feet of eight inch water maintenance, these
streets south of West Timer. Yes, or as part of the permit DQ just asked this to be recognized
in the meeting minutes, so it is on the Agina tonight for acknowledgment. Okay, although they are
sort of leading to flow. Yes, sir, this is just needs to be acknowledged in the minutes. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Question, is there any way to bore the water lines? Or is this open-trench dig of that?
Actually, we're here going to bore some of that water line. We've been growing a water line
in on D Street from Central to Fourth. And so then we're getting ready to go over and do E Street
Northwest from Third to Central. Okay. Next, and then we'll do this one. So we have the
morning unit, the citybot, three or four or five years ago, and we've actually got it out and started
using it. So if that's some time, if you'd like to see it in action, we'd like to show it to you.
I've seen the pipe down at the park and I'd really like to watch that go in there. Yes, sir. We'll
tell you whenever we're going to go in and we'll go back to that. Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't even love
any other new business, any new business, being anyone? No, you're honoured. Any trust
taking me to the announcements? No, sir. I don't know. I don't know if I was a German, but
most of the time, most of the time. Second. Second. Old ball plays for it, sir. Bye.